Hi,
Hank
Rogers,
Bulletproof
Software.
It...
Hello,
is...
Hank.
an
honor
Minoru
Arakawa,
to
be
president
here.
of
Nintendo
America.
Hank...?
Goddamn
Rogers.
Welcome
to...
Seattle.
Howard
Lincoln,
senior
VP,
chief
legal
counsel.
Your
cowboy
reputation
precedes
you.
Here,
sign
this.
An
NDA?
Why?
Because
only
ten
other
people
in
the
world
have
seen
what
you're
about
to
see,
and
to
be
honest...
we
don't
trust
you.
8-bit
graphics...?
Yes...
and
a
brand
new
Sharp
LR35902
core
at
4.19
megahertz
with
kilobytes
internal
RAM.
Impressive.
No
Color,
color
screen?
you
need
eight
batteries
instead
of
four.
It's
too
expensive.
This
gives
you
hours
of
gameplay,
all
for
$89.
What's...
It's
it
called?
called
the
Game
Boy.
Go
ahead,
try
it.
We're
launching
in
June,
and
we
want
publishers
like
lookout
for
new
games.
So...
you'll
package
it
with
Mario?
Yes...
it's
our
best
brand.
This
game
is
programmed
in
C...
yeah?
Mm-hmm.
How
many...
pixels?
by
144.
Why?
It's
not
perfect,
but
you'll
get
the
idea.
Gentlemen,
if
you
want
to
sell
a
couple
hundred
thousand
Game
Boys
to
little
kids...
package
them
with
Mario.
But
if
you
want
to
sell
millions
of
Game
Boys
to
absolutely
everyone,
young
and
old,
around
the
world...
package
them
with
Tetris.
rights?